<property name="documentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.DocAttribute">
    <property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="Edward A. Lee (eal@eecs.berkeley.edu)">
    </property>
    <property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="&lt;p&gt;Accessor to play an audio signal.&#10; This accessor accepts as input in a variety of formats and plays&#10; back the audio encoded in those input values.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt; This accessor queues the data to be played by the audio system.&#10; When the data has been accepted by the audio system to be played,&#10; it produces an output with value true. That output should be used&#10; as a trigger to provide more audio data. If that new output data&#10; is provided before the previously data has been drained by the audio&#10; queue, then continuous audio with no gaps is possible.&#10; If on the other hand input data is provided too quickly, then it&#10; will overwrite the data in the output buffer, thereby creating&#10; considerable distortion. If it is provided too slowly, then there&#10; will be gaps in the output audio.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt; The &lt;em&gt;inputFormat&lt;/em&gt; parameter specifies the form in which the audio&#10; input will be provided. The available formats include:&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;ul&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;raw&amp;quot;: The input is a byte array representing audio data exactly as&#10;captured by default on the host.&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;array&amp;quot;: The audio input data is an array of arrays of numbers,&#10;where each number is in the range from -1.0 to 1.0.&#10;The first index of the input specifies the channel number.&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;encoded&amp;quot;: The audio input data is a byte array containing audio&#10;data encoded in one of the file format standards such as&#10;AIFF (historically associated with Apple computers),&#10;AIFF-C (a compressed version of AIFF),&#10;AU (historically associated with Sun Microsystems and Unix computers), or&#10;WAVE (historically associated with Windows PCs).&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;playbackOptions&lt;/em&gt; parameter is an object with the following properties,&#10;all of which are optional:&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;bigEndian&lt;/em&gt;: 1 if the the sample is big endian, 0 if it is little endian&#10;If &lt;em&gt;bigEndian&lt;/em&gt; is not present, then the default is big endian.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;bitsPerSample&lt;/em&gt;: The number of bits per sample. This is an integer that&#10;defaults to 16.&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;channels&lt;/em&gt;: The number of channels. This defaults to 1.&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;sampleRate&lt;/em&gt;: The sample rate. This is an integer that defaults to 8000.&#10;Typical supported sample rates are 8000, 11025, 22050, 44100, and 48000.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;WAVE (aka .wav) is 16 bits, 1 channel, little endian, 44100 Hz.&#10;This accessor requires the optional &apos;audio&apos; module, which may or may&#10;not be provided by an accessor host. Moreover, a host may not support&#10;all capture formats and all output formats.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;/ul&gt;">
    </property>
    <property name="input (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="undefined" value="The audio data.">
    </property>
    <property name="accepted (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="undefined" value="An indicator that the audio data has been queued&#10;  to the audio system.">
    </property>
    <property name="inputFormat (parameter)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="undefined" value="The format of the input data.">
    </property>
    <property name="playbackOptions (parameter)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="undefined" value="The playback options.">
    </property>
    <property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="$$Id$$">
    </property>
</property>