<property name="documentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.DocAttribute">
    <property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="Anne H. Ngu (angu@txstate.edu)">
    </property>
    <property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="&lt;p&gt;This accessor discovers REST services on the web and and generates a concrete&#10;REST accessor for the service. It requires the contextAware module and&#10;interface definition of concrete REST services. Please see:&#10;https://&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.icyphy.org/accessors/wiki/Version0/ContextAware&quot;&gt;www.icyphy.org/accessors/wiki/Version0/ContextAware&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Example usage of ContextAware accessor:&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;This accessor generalizes the capability of REST.js by providing a simple&#10;interface for a user to select a concrete REST service and provides the&#10;context (set of inputs needed) to invoke that concrete REST service and set&#10;of outputs needed from the service.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Currently it is coded for three concrete REST services (GSN, Firebase, and&#10;Paraimpu), but can be expanded to any number of REST services as long as the&#10;interface of the service can be defined. The three services that this&#10;accessor works with are the GSN, which is a global sensor network server&#10;hosted in Texas State university, the Paraimpu which is a social aware&#10;middleware for Internet of Things and Firebase which is a cloud service from&#10;Google that provides storage for IoT.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;This is just an experimental system, so the UI is very primitive and basic.&#10;To experiment with it, do the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;ul&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt; double click on the accessor, make a selection, press commit,&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt; double click on the accessor, press the reload button and then press&#10;commit,&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt; double click again and the required input for the selected REST service&#10;will appear on the editor menu&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt; for GSN, enter &apos;pluto.cs.txstate.edu&apos; for the host, enter &apos;22001&apos; for&#10;the port, select the specific output dataType or leave it as &amp;quot;all&amp;quot;. Leave the&#10;rest as default&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt; for Paraimpu, enter &apos;api.paraimpu.com&apos; for the host, enter &apos;443&apos; for the&#10;port, enter this &lt;code&gt;46e0ee55195c4dd9dca295a7ac8282d28f4a2259&lt;/code&gt; for&#10;access token. Select the dataType for output or leave it as &apos;all&apos;&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt; for Firebase, enter &apos;sizzling-fire-8605.firebaseio.com&apos; for the host,&#10;enter &apos;443&apos; for port, leave the rest as default. Select the appropriate&#10;dataType to output or leave it as &apos;all&apos;. &lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;/ul&gt;">
    </property>
    <property name="input (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="[object Object]" value="to the accessor">
    </property>
    <property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="$$Id$$">
    </property>
</property>