<property name="documentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.DocAttribute">
    <property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="Edward A. Lee (eal@eecs.berkeley.edu), contributor: Christopher Brooks">
    </property>
    <property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="&lt;p&gt;Accessor for RESTful interfaces.&#10; Upon receipt of a trigger input, this accessor will issue an HTTP request&#10; specified by the inputs. Some time later, the accessor will receive a response&#10; from the server or a timeout. In the first case, the accessor will produce&#10; the response (body, status code, and headers) on output ports.&#10; In the second case, it will produce a nil output on the response port&#10; and an error.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt; The accessor does not block waiting for the response, but any additional&#10; triggered requests will be queued to be issued only after the pending request&#10; has received either a response or a timeout. This strategy ensures that outputs&#10; from this accessor are produced in the same order as the inputs that trigger the&#10; HTTP requests.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt; The &lt;i&gt;options&lt;/i&gt; input can be a string URL (with surrounding quotation marks)&#10; or an object with the following fields:&#10; &lt;ul&gt;&#10; &lt;li&gt; headers: An object containing request headers. By default this&#10;      is an empty object. Items may have a value that is an array of values,&#10;      for headers with more than one value.&#10; &lt;li&gt; keepAlive: A boolean that specified whether to keep sockets around&#10;      in a pool to be used by other requests in the future. This defaults to false.&#10; &lt;li&gt; method: A string specifying the HTTP request method.&#10;      This defaults to &apos;GET&apos;, but can also be &apos;PUT&apos;, &apos;POST&apos;, &apos;DELETE&apos;, etc.&#10; &lt;li&gt; url: A string that can be parsed as a URL, or an object containing&#10;      the following fields:&#10;      &lt;ul&gt;&#10;      &lt;li&gt; host: A string giving the domain name or IP address of&#10;           the server to issue the request to. This defaults to &apos;localhost&apos;.&#10;      &lt;li&gt; protocol: The protocol. This is a string that defaults to &apos;http&apos;.&#10;      &lt;li&gt; port: Port of remote server. This defaults to 80.&#10;      &lt;/ul&gt;&#10; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt; For example, the &lt;i&gt;options&lt;/i&gt; parameter could be set to&#10; &lt;code&gt;&#10; {&amp;quot;headers&amp;quot;:{&amp;quot;Content-Type&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;application/x-www-form-urlencoded&amp;quot;}, &amp;quot;method&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;POST&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;url&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;...&amp;quot;}&#10; &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt; In addition, there is a &lt;i&gt;command&lt;/i&gt; input that is a string that is appended&#10; as a path to the URL constructed from the &lt;i&gt;options&lt;/i&gt; input. This defaults&#10; to the empty string.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt; The &lt;i&gt;arguments&lt;/i&gt; input an object with fields that are converted to a query&#10; string to append to the url, for example &apos;?arg=value&apos;. If the value contains&#10; characters that are not allowed in a URL, such as spaces, they will encoded&#10; according to the ASCII standard, see http://&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.w3schools.com/tags/ref_urlencode.asp&quot;&gt;www.w3schools.com/tags/ref_urlencode.asp&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt; A &lt;i&gt;trigger&lt;/i&gt; input triggers invocation of the current command. Any value provided&#10; on the trigger input is ignored.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt; The output response will be a string if the MIME type of the accessed page&#10; begins with &amp;quot;text&amp;quot;. If the MIME type begins with anything else, then the&#10; binary data will be produced. It is up to the host implementation to ensure&#10; that the data is given in some form that is usable by downstream accessors&#10; or actors.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt; The parameter &apos;timeout&apos; specifies how long this accessor will wait for response.&#10; If it does not receive the response by the specified time, then it will issue&#10; a null response output and an error event (calling the error() function of the host).&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt; If the parameter &apos;outputCompleteResponseOnly&apos; is true (the default), then this&#10; accessor will produce a &apos;response&apos; output only upon receiving a complete response.&#10; If it is false, then multiple outputs may result from a single input or trigger.&lt;/p&gt;">
    </property>
    <property name="options (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="[object Object]" value="The url for the command or an object specifying options.">
    </property>
    <property name="command (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="[object Object]" value="The command.">
    </property>
    <property name="arguments (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="[object Object]" value="Arguments to the command.">
    </property>
    <property name="body (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="undefined" value="The request body, if any.  This supports at least strings and image data.">
    </property>
    <property name="trigger (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="undefined" value="An input to trigger the command.">
    </property>
    <property name="response (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="[object Object]" value="The server&apos;s response.">
    </property>
    <property name="status (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="[object Object]" value="The status code and message of the response.">
    </property>
    <property name="headers (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="undefined" value="The headers sent with the response.">
    </property>
    <property name="timeout (parameter)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="[object Object]" value="The amount of time (in milliseconds) to wait for a response&#10;  before triggering a null response and an error. This defaults to 5000.">
    </property>
    <property name="outputCompleteResponseOnly (parameter)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="[object Object]" value="If true (the default), the produce a&#10;  &apos;response&apos; output only upon receiving the entire response.">
    </property>
    <property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="$$Id$$">
    </property>
</property>