<property name="documentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.DocAttribute">
    <property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="Patricia Derler, Edward A. Lee, Ben Zhang">
    </property>
    <property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="&lt;p&gt;Publish to a Vert.x event bus, which is a peer-to-peer publish-and-subscribe system.&#10; The published data will be sent to any subscriber that subscribes to the same&#10; address and runs in the same Vertx cluster (see the VertxSubscribe accessor).&#10; The Vertx cluster normally includes all machines that hear multicast packets&#10; sent by the machine hosting this accessor.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt; The input to be published can be any data type supported by accessors that&#10; has a string representation in JSON syntax. The data will be converted to a&#10; string in JSON format and sent to the event bus. The VertxSubscribe accessor&#10; will parse that string and output the data in the native format of its host.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt; If the broadcast input is set to false, then instead of broadcasting the&#10; message to all subscribers, the Vertx bus will pick exactly one subscriber&#10; and send the message to it.  The bus picks the subscribers in an approximately&#10; round-robin fashion. If the subscriber replies to this message, then that&#10; will reply (required to be also be a JSON object) will be produced on the&#10; reply output port.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt; The busHost input specifies the name of the network interface through which&#10; to connect to the Vert.x event bus cluster, and busHostPort specifies the&#10; port to use for this. Normally, you can leave these at their default values&#10; unless you need to need to use a network interface that is not &apos;localhost&apos;&#10; or you need to use a particular port. These two inputs are examined only&#10; at initialization time, so changing them during execution of a swarmlet&#10; will have no effect.&lt;/p&gt;">
    </property>
    <property name="address (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="[object Object]" value="The event bus address, which is the name of the event stream.&#10;  This defaults to &apos;topic&apos;.">
    </property>
    <property name="message (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="undefined" value="The message to publish.">
    </property>
    <property name="broadcast (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="[object Object]" value="Indicator of whether to send to all subscribers or just one.&#10;  This defaults to true, which means to send to all subscribers.">
    </property>
    <property name="reply (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="undefined" value="The reply, if any, received after a point-to-point send&#10;  (where broadcast == false).">
    </property>
    <property name="busHost (parameter)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="[object Object]" value="The name of the network interface to use for the Vert.x&#10;  event bus. A blank string is interpreted as &apos;localhost&apos; (the default).">
    </property>
    <property name="busHostPort (parameter)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" type="[object Object]" value="The port for the Vert.x event bus. A value of 0&#10;  indicates to just find an available port (the default).">
    </property>
    <property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="$$Id$$">
    </property>
</property>